That
walking is a perfect option for people of all ages, some
walk for their digestion, some for
their blood pressure, there
are a lot of special benefits of walking, but has your
walking ever benefited someone else?
ICICI Lombard, on this World
Health Day, gave India such a unique
opportunity with the Donate Your Steps Initiative,
a university through which anyone
can feed a needy child by walking a few steps. People started sharing their steps on the Come and Take Care app
on Twitter.
As soon as someone's thousand tips were completed, we
fed a needy child nutritious food. Within no time,
thousands of people started
joining us and started walking. In just one week, there were
1.5 crore
strikes on Come and Take Care and gave an
opportunity to eat nutritious food to about 20,000 needy children.
That your every step brings peace to these children.
Your every step gives these children a
reason to smile.
Om Shanti Om.
I thank your show
Ajay from the bottom of my
heart and every companion who walked with us in the 10 Steps Initiative
and will continue to do so, light the
flame of humanity, step by step.  We will keep burning and will
keep our promises as always. Do it, do it.